(Leonard(Penny sneezes):)-Getting a cold?
-No, no, it's probably just allergies.
(Leonard:)You want an allergy pill?
I have them all.
(Leonard:)Prescription, nonprescription, foreign,
domestic, experimental.
(Penny:)Do any of them work?
(Leonard:)Not really, I'm just an enthusiast.
[BLOWS NOSE]
[PENNY RETCHES]
(Raj:)Penny?
[TOILET FLUSHES]
(Leonard:)You okay?
PENNY:
Did that sound okay to you?
(Penny:)Do not come in here.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
PENNY: I'm having a tea party.
What do you think is going on?
[PENNY HAWKS AND SPITS]
(Penny:)I think I might have the flu.
[PENNY VOMITS]
(Penny:)Or the plague.
(Leonard:)Well, our plane leaves at 9 a.m.
Do you think you'll feel better by then?